#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/inesvazpereira (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Project Management Quality Management MS Project

## Languages

Spanish (Professional Working) English (Professional Working) Portuguese (Native or Bilingual)

#### Certifications

Lean Implementation Leader - White Belt

# Inês Vaz Pereira

Partner | Consulting - People Consulting at EY Lisbon, Lisbon, Portugal

# Summary

Welcome!

I am Partner at EY S.A., responsible for the People Consulting practice. I take responsibility for managing multiple teams divided into:

- a) People Consulting HR specialized team in Strategic Human Resources Consulting, global and local existing in Portugal, Angola and Mozambique.
- b) People Consulting SYSTEMS EY Digital HR Near Shore Hub in Portugal supporting more than 20 countries in the EY EMEIA cluster. Team specialized in projects implementation with focus on Digital HR Transformation through technology such as SAP SuccessFactors, SAP Concur, ServiceNow, Microsoft Viva, among others.

I have experienced managing HR transformation with a demonstrated history of working in cross-industry. Working "with" and "for" people is my motivation.

All my professional experiences have turned me into a very dedicated person, 100% committed, strong oriented towards results and always very demanding with myself and the team. I am grateful for all of them!

Peter F. Drucker said, "Management is doing things right; leadership is doing the right things".

I would just add: "(...) leadership is doing the right things" based on four principles: respect, understanding, acceptance and appreciation.

Let me know your thoughts... it will be a pleasure to meet you!

# Experience

#### EY

3 years 9 months

Partner | Consulting - People Consulting at EY July 2023 - Present (1 year 10 months)
Portugal

Partner at EY for People Consulting : Human Capital Services - Portugal, Angola and Mozambique.

Humans are the center of everything we do!

Associate Partner - People Advisory Services August 2021 - June 2023 (1 year 11 months) Portugal

People Advisory Services - Workforce Advisory Services

- Team specialized in Strategic Human Resources Consulting, global and local existing in Portugal, Angola and Mozambique.

People Advisory Services - Systems

1st EY Digital HR Near Shore Hub in Portugal supporting more than
 20 countries in the EY EMEIA cluster. Team specialized in projects implementation with focus on Digital HR Transformation – through technology such as SAP SuccessFactors, SAP Concur, ServiceNow, Microsoft Viva, among others.

#### SAP

Account Executive Expert - FSI & RETAIL January 2021 - July 2021 (7 months)
Portugal

SAP for Banking Industry SAP for Insurance Industry SAP for Retail Industry

SAP Concur SAP CONCUR - Regional Sales Executive for Portugal January 2020 - January 2021 (1 year 1 month) Lisbon Area, Portugal

SAP SuccessFactors
2 years 11 months
HR CLOUD Solution Sale

HR CLOUD Solution Sales Expert February 2019 - January 2020 (1 year)

Lisbon Area, Portugal

# SAP SuccessFactors Sales Manager | Portugal & French Africa April 2018 - February 2019 (11 months)

Lisbon Area, Portugal

Head of SAP SuccessFactors for Portugal March 2017 - March 2018 (1 year 1 month) Portugal

SAP Portugal Head of Cloud Business December 2015 - March 2017 (1 year 4 months) Porto Salvo

Talentia Software
Portugal Managing Director
March 2013 - December 2015 (2 years 10 months)

Cezanne Software - Portugal
Project Manager
April 2011 - March 2013 (2 years)
Project Management and Customer Support

Barclays Bank Portugal

Project Manager
February 2007 - March 2011 (4 years 2 months)

Lean Implementation Leader: create and execute reengineering projects

Manage day-to-day project operational criteria

Project and process efficiency methodologies (LEAN, ITIL, CMMI, etc).

Project budget management.

Indra Sistemas Portugal, S.A.
Quality Management
February 2005 - February 2007 (2 years 1 month)
Implementação e Gestão dos Processos de Gestão da Qualidade
Formação e motivação de equipas
Auditoria Internas & Auditorias Externas
Reporting e Folow-up de métricas

Sinase Quality Technician February 2003 - January 2005 (2 years)

Apoio na Gestão dos Processos de Gestão da Qualidade.

Consultoria em Gestão da Qualidade

# Education

Católica Lisbon School of Business and Economics Formação Executivos, Programa Desenvolvimento Liderança · (October 2021 - December 2021)

### BTS Faculty - Dubai, Emirates

Lead Teams to Great Results, Leadership & Management Practice for high perform teams · (July 2019 - July 2019)

#### APOGEP /KnowNow Portugal

Project Management - PMBOOK, Project Management skills · (October 2010 - March 2011)

#### ABSA BANK – Johannesburg, South Africa

Performance Improvement Leader Training , Lean Methodology Certification Programme applied to Banking Business Process & IT systems · (September 2008 - September 2008)

## Indeg\_ISCTE Business School

Post-Graduation, Business Management · (2006 - 2007)